# Joseph Rohman

# Technical Project Manager

I am a certified fullstack software engineer, with a degree in Advertising, and proven experience as a highly-effective and efficient project manager. I seek out challenges and I have a passion for business development and product design.

## **Work History**

### 2019-03 -Current

## Freelance Web Developer

JHRohman, Daly City, California

- Successfully creates websites leveraging user-focus designer and brand marketing strategies.
- Full-stack developer with primary languages: React, HTML, CSS, & Javascript, and secondary languages Python/Django, Node.js
- Experience with MongoDB, Heroku, Postgres, & SQL

## 2015-06 -Current

#### Freelance CAD Drafter

JHRohman, Daly City, California

- Superior knowledge of design and production process
- Working closely with clients or team members to turn vague ideas into full production-ready products
- Consistently generates build-documents and 3D renderings that can be understood by anyone, of any discipline, or speaking any language

## 2011-06 -Current

## Freelance Graphic Designer

JHRohman, Daly City, California

- Succeeding in translating complex ideas & motivations into compelling, modern designs
- Leveraging Advertising degree & design background to spearhead client marketing projects
- Effectively collaborates with wide range of individuals from designers to executives.

#### 2017-06 -2019-02

## **Project Manager**

Blueprint Studios, San Bruno, CA

- Directed the department of 15 people, managed 50 vendors, supporting all other departments, and completing over 600 events in 2 years
- Created automated record & scheduling system, giving department back 25% of our time, increasing the transparency of budgeting, and increasing the accuracy of project forecast
- Orchestrated departmental business development,

## **Personal Info**

#### **Address**

San Francisco Bay Area, California

#### E-mail

josephhrohman@gmail.com

#### Skills

Leadership

Time Management

Trello

Public Speaking

Risk Management

Github

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript ES6, React.js

Rhino 5 3D CAD Software

Adobe Creative Suite

**Business Development** 

**Brand Marketing** 

Advanced problem solving

Strategic planning

Operations management

Project management

Graphic design

Market analysis

interfacing with clients such as Google, Adobe, and Facebook; commonly returning between 500% - 1200% profit per project

 Risk Manager; the go-to person to call for solutions across all production departments and client crises. Was requested to be on company 'think-tank' for crisis resolution

## **Education**

2013-08 - 2016-12	Bachelor of Arts: Advertising
	University of San Francisco - San Francisco, CA
2019-03 - 2019-06	Certification: Fullstack Software Engineering
	General Assembly San Francisco - San Francisco, CA